<_>
   <form_key>tYrbwRhPQfSujwPA</form_key>
   <name>Payin7_Payments</name>
   <channel>community</channel>
   <version_ids>
      <version_ids>2</version_ids>
   </version_ids>
   <summary>Payin7 offers the clients the opportunity of choosing between two products: Pay in 7 days or Finance Payment (http://www.payin7.com)

----

Payin7 ofrece a los clientes la oportunidad de elegir entre dos productos: Pago en 7 días o Pago financiado</summary>
   <description>PAYIN7 offers the clients the opportunity of choosing between two forms of payment:

1. PAYMENT IN 7 DAYS allows clients to pay after they have received their products. 
2. FINANCE PAYMENT clients can pay for their products with downpayments - from 2 to 6 installments.

- NO NEED TO USE  A CREDIT CARD - The clients can choose not to use their credit card which gives a greater confidence in payment.
- ACCESS TO EXPENSIVE PRODUCTS - Clients may purchase products which otherwise they could not afford. Wide range of products at their choice.
- GIFTS TO YOUR CLIENTS FOR FINANCING – Using gamification and other promotions and offer them to the clients who use our products.
- QUICK AND EASY INTEGRATION – Starting up with our platform is fast – only a few minutes are necessary.
- COMPATIBLE WITH OTHER PAYMENT METHODS – You can keep using paypal, credit card or any other payment system.
- SALES PROMOTIONS - Use the possibility of financing as a marketing tool.
- DIFFERENTIATE FROM YOUR COMPETITORS – Always be one step ahead of your competitors.
- ACCESS TO NEW CLIENTS - A wider range of customers will pay for more expensive products.

----

PAYIN7 ofrece a sus clientes la financiación de sus ventas a través de dos productos de pago:

1. Con PAGO EN 7 DIAS el cliente podrá pagar una vez recibida la mercancía. 
2. Con PAGO FINANCIADO el cliente final divide sus pagos entre 2 y 6 cuotas.

- SIN NECESIDAD DE USAR UNA TARJETA DE CREDITO – El cliente final puede optar a usar o no su tarjeta de crédito en sus compras.  Dándole mayor confianza en el pago.
- ACESSO A PRODUCTOS ANTES NO ASUMIBLES – Tu cliente podrá adquirir productos que de otra manera no podrían asumir.  Amplia la gama de productos a su alcance.
- REGALOS PARA TUS CLIENTES POR FINANCIARSE – Realizamos sorteos entre tus clientes lo cual aumentará tus ventas. 
- INTEGRACION SENCILLA Y RAPIDA – En pocos minutos podrás empezar a operar con nosotros. 
- COMPATIBLE CON OTROS METODOS DE PAGO – Compatible con paypal, VISA o cualquier otro sistema de pago. 
- PROMOCIONES QUE BENEFICIAN LAS VENTAS DE LOS ECOMMERCE – Usa la posibilidad de financiar como herramienta de marketing. 
- DIFERENCIACION CON LA COMPETENCIA – Ve un paso por delante de tus competidores. 
- ACESSO A NUEVOS CLIENTES – La posibilidad de financiar abre tu ecommerce a nuevos clientes. Un mayor rango de clientes van a pagar por tus productos más costosos.</description>
   <license>GNU General Public License (GPL)</license>
   <license_uri>http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.en.html</license_uri>
   <version>1.0.0.0</version>
   <stability>stable</stability>
   <notes>First release of the extension.

If you are not a customer yet but would like to become one email: info@payin7.com.

Report bugs and issues to: support@payin7.com.</notes>
   <authors>
      <name>
         <name>Payin7.com</name>
         <name>Nimasystems Ltd</name>
      </name>
      <user>
         <user>payin7</user>
         <user>nimasystems</user>
      </user>
      <email>
         <email>info@payin7.com</email>
         <email>info@nimasystems.com</email>
      </email>
   </authors>
   <depends_php_min>5.4.6</depends_php_min>
   <depends_php_max>6.0.0</depends_php_max>
   <depends>
      <package>
         <name>
            <name/>
            <name>Mage_Payment</name>
         </name>
         <channel>
            <channel/>
            <channel/>
         </channel>
         <min>
            <min/>
            <min/>
         </min>
         <max>
            <max/>
            <max/>
         </max>
         <files>
            <files>                            </files>
            <files>                            </files>
         </files>
      </package>
      <extension>
         <name>
            <name>Core</name>
         </name>
         <min>
            <min/>
         </min>
         <max>
            <max/>
         </max>
      </extension>
   </depends>
   <contents>
      <target>
         <target>magelocal</target>
         <target>magecommunity</target>
         <target>magedesign</target>
         <target>magedesign</target>
         <target>magedesign</target>
         <target>magedesign</target>
         <target>mageetc</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
         <target>magelocale</target>
         <target>mageskin</target>
         <target>mageskin</target>
         <target>mageskin</target>
         <target>mageskin</target>
         <target>magelib</target>
         <target>magelib</target>
         <target>magelib</target>
         <target>magelib</target>
         <target>magelib</target>
         <target>magelib</target>
      </target>
      <path>
         <path/>
         <path>Payin7</path>
         <path>adminhtml/default/default/layout/payin7payments.xml</path>
         <path>adminhtml/default/default/template/payin7payments</path>
         <path>frontend/base/default/layout/payin7payments.xml</path>
         <path>frontend/base/default/template/payin7payments</path>
         <path>modules/Payin7_Payments.xml</path>
         <path>en_US/Payin7_Payments.csv</path>
         <path>es_ES/Payin7_Payments.csv</path>
         <path>adminhtml/default/default/css/payin7</path>
         <path>frontend/base/default/css/payin7</path>
         <path>frontend/base/default/images/payin7</path>
         <path>frontend/base/default/js/payin7</path>
         <path>Payin7/payin7-php/CHANGELOG</path>
         <path>Payin7/payin7-php/LICENSE</path>
         <path>Payin7/payin7-php/README.md</path>
         <path>Payin7/payin7-php/vendor</path>
         <path>Payin7/payin7-php/src</path>
         <path>Payin7/utils</path>
      </path>
      <type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>file</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>dir</type>
         <type>dir</type>
      </type>
      <include>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
         <include/>
      </include>
      <ignore>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
         <ignore/>
      </ignore>
   </contents>
</_>
